Salem Witchcraft Papers from the Massachusetts Historical Society
University of Virginia Library
Salem Witchcraft Papers from the Massachusetts Historical Society
Massachusetts Historical Society
- Documents In The Salem Witchcraft Papers
  - Boroughs, George Warrant, 1
  - Hutchinson, Elisha Letter 2 may 1692, 2
  - Hubbard, Wolcott, Putnam, v George Boroughs, 3
  - Walcott, Vibber, Lewis, Putnam, Hubbard v George Boroughs 9, May, 1692, 4
  - Lewis, Walcott, Hubbard, Putnam. v. George Boroughs 9, May, 1692, 5
  - Hobbs, A. v. George Boroughs 1 June 1692, 6a
  - Walcott, Mary v. George Boroughs 3 August, 7a
  - John Pierce & John Lane; George Boroughs, summons 4 August, v 1692., 7b
  - Warren, Mary v. George Boroughs 3 August, 8
  - Webber, Mary v. George Boroughs 2 August 1692, 9
  - Greinslitt, Thomas 15 Sept. 1692, 10
  - Putnam, Thomas; Putnam, Edward v. George Boroughs, 11a
  - Hubbard, Eliz v. Mary Bradbury 9 Sept. 1692, 11b
  - Putnam, Ann v. Mary Bradbury 9 Sept. 1692, 12a
  - Walcott, Mary v. Mary Bradbury, 12b
  - Vibber, Sarah v. Mary Bradbury, 13
  - Lewis, Mercy v.Martha Cory 4 March 1692, 14
  - Walcott, Mary; Hubbard, Elizabeth, Putnam, Ann v. Martha Carrier, 15
  - Rogers, John, et al Summons 29 June, 16a
  - Williams, Abigail v. Martha Kory, 31 May 1692, 16b
  - Hubbard, Eliz. v. Martha Carrier, 1 July 1692, 17a
  - Walcott, Mary v. Martha Carrier, 1 July 1692, 17b
  - Capt. Danforth Rogers, John Summons, 18
  - Hubbard, Eliz. v. Martha Cory, 4 August 1692, 19
  - Putnam, Edward v. Martha Cory 14 march 1692, 20
  - Putnam, Thomas; Putnam, John v. Martha Carrier, 21a
  - Horton, Andrew v. Carrier & Toothacker, 21b
  - Lewis, Mercy; Hubbard, Elizabeth v. Goody Cory, 22a
  - Vibber, Sarah 30 June, 1692, 22b
  - Andrew, Sarah v. Elizabeth How, 2 June 1692, 23a
  - Williams, Abigail v. George Jacobs, Sr. 10 May 1692, 23b
  - Lewis, Walcott, Hubbard, Putnam, Churchill v. Geo. Jacobs, 4 August 1692, 24
  - Hobs, William; Bishop, Edward, Wild, Sarah Summons, 25
  - Putnam, Thomas, Putnam,John V. George Jacobs, 26a
  - Putnam, Ann v. George Jacobs, 26b
  - Derich, John v. George Jacobs, 27
  - Fox, Rebecka For Rebecka Jacobs, 28
  - Bradford, Wm & Rachell v. Mercy Lewis, 29a
  - Putnam, Nathaniel For Rebecca Nurse, 29b
  - Porter, Israel et al For Rebecca Nurse, 30
  - Parker, Alice Examination, 31
  - Warren, Mary v. Alice Parker 6 Sept. 1692, 32
  - Walcott, Mary v. Alice parker, 33
  - Vibber, Walcott, Hubbard v. Alice Parker 7 Sept 1692, 34
  - Philips, Sarah v. Mary Parker 31 August 1692, 35
  - Towne Family Summons 6 Sept. 1692, 36
  - Huchinson, Josiah Re: Abigail Williams, 37a
  - Nurse, Sarah v. Sarah Vibber 29 June 1692, 37b
- Documents in Miscellaneous Manuscripts
  - Hubbard, Eliz. v. Abigail Row, Esther Elwell, Rebecca Dike, Nov. 8, 1692
  - Restitution Document
  - Eames, Daniel Examination 13 August 1692, Aug. 13, 1692
  - Burroughs, George Examination 9 May 1692, May 9, 1692
  - Warren, Mary v. Daniel Ames, January 1693, Jan. 1693